DUC DUNG BUI

INTERN SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

OVERVIEW

Senior student of the Faculty of Information Technology, majoring in Computer Science of Ton Duc Thang University want to follow software developer career. I am very sociable and energetic, love sports and spend most of my free time in the gym or playing soccer. With the desire to learn and experience the real environment. Hope I can bring value to the business.

EDUCATIONS

Ton Duc Thang University

August 2018 - Now

• Major: Computer Science

• Expected graduation: September 2024

• GPA: 7.1/10

(Software technology: 7.1, Systems analysis and design: 7.7, Introduction to Artificial Intelligence: 7.0, Introduction to Machine Learning: 7.3, Mobile application development: 7.53, Web and App Programming: 7.0, Introduction to Information Security: 8.0, Introduction to Computer Security: 6.5)

PROJECTS

■ Mobile application development class

Music application | April 2023 - May 2023

- Navigation menu to Home, New Song, Albums, Artist, Personal Music Fragment.
- Search Songs and Albums.
- Player view and mini player view of song.
- Like and unlike song.
- Personal Music Fragment stores user's liked songs.
- Edit User's information (Name, phone, email, address, avatar), Send email to change User's password.

Technologies:

- Using Android Studio IDE, java, XML, dependencies.
- Using Firebase to save data and design database.



CONTACT ME AT



+84 903726918



ducdungbui1712@gmail.com



Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam



https://github.com/ducdungb ui1712



https://www.linkedin.com/in/d %C5%A9ng-b%C3%B9i-71a3a3264/

SKILLS SUMMARY

Programming language

• Python, Java, C, C#

Front End

 JavaScript, Html, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap

Back End

• Python, PHP

Database

• SQL Server, MySQL, Firebase

Source control

• GitHub

Source code:

• https://github.com/ducdungbui1712/MusicApplica
tionAndroid

■ Systems analysis and design class

Real-Time Continuous Glucose Monitoring (RTCGM) | April 2022 - May 2022

 In this project, we will introduce to you how a Real-Time Continuous Glucose Monitoring (RTCGM) can be built from scratch. From what the system requirements and how to meet them, to declaring all the use cases and its actors. Represent contents through use case diagrams, activity diagrams, sequence diagrams,.... We also build an assumption of all the UI that the system needs.

Source code:

 https://github.com/ducdungbui1712/Systems An alysis and Design Class Final Project

■ Web and app programming class

Cloning Topzone website (demo version) | March 2022 - May 2022

- Search product using ajax
- Navigation menu.
- Click to see product detail information.
- · Apply motion effect for navbar.
- Drag or click left/right to see more products.

Technologies:

• Front-end: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery.

• Back-end: PHP.

Database: MySQL (XAMPP)

Source code:

 https://github.com/ducdungbui1712/Web Class Topzone-clone final project

■ Software technology class

Dietary Supplement MVC website | October 2022 - December 2022

- Webform ASP.net MVC for customers to buy products.
- WinForms C# for accountants to manage customer's orders.
- Webform ASP.net MVC: login, logout, register an account, change pass, place orders, view cart.
- WinForms C#: login, change password. When use accountant account will log to accountant WinForms, use admin account will log to admin WinForms.
- Accountant WinForms: view by date/month/year of product list/customer's orders list/customer's orders detail, add/change products, export file of

- Good Python programing skills with data analysis libraries: pandas, NumPy, seaborn, matplotlib, Sklearn,...
- Good knowledge about Data structures & Algorithms, Probability & statistics, Algebra, Database.
- Good at systems analysis and design, using variation of diagram (Use Case, ERD, business, Modeling diagram,...).
- Good at English, can read English documents and communicate well.
- Sociable and energetic. Good concentration on working. High self-learning and adaptability.

goods import invoice/delivery invoice/delivery details.

 Admin WinForms: view product list, view accountants/customers accounts include their information, add new accountant.

Technologies:

 WinForms C#, ASP.net, .NET framework, SQL.

Video demo application:

 https://drive.google.com/file/d/1CoRZSv PQ20lyTG4ch0S7EKOPk6eA7hbZ/view? usp=share link

Source code:

• https://github.com/ducdungbui1712/Sotf wareTechnology Class Final Project

■ Machine learning class

Stock price prediction | November 2022 - December 2022

Use the stock dataset of Amazon,
 Facebook and Netflix from 2015-2019 from
 Kaggle. Compare the stock price of these
 three companies and predict the stock
 price of each company.

Technologies:

• Python.

Source code:

 https://github.com/ducdungbui1712/Mach ineLearning Class Final Project

■ Artificial intelligence class

Final project (2 exercises) | September 2022 - November 2022

- Exercise 1: write a program to solve the traveler problem (TSP) using genetic algorithm with distance in 2 cases: smallest, largest.
- Exercise 2: NFL 1st and Future Impact Detection on Kaggle.

Technologies:

• Python.

Source code:

https://github.com/ducdungbui1712/AI Class Final Project

WORK EXPERIENCE

Shift leader Cristal Jade restaurant | August 2018 - Jun 2019

Sale manager of local brand Lesavril de Vetements | August 2019 - January 2021

• https://www.facebook.com/lesavril.de.vetements

Shopee affiliate | January 2021 - December 2021